James F. McNulty Papers, 1925-2002
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 2: Volunteer Activity, 1958-1983
  - Series 4: Arizona State Board of Education, 1965 – 1977
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, August 1966 – September 1966 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, October 1966 – November 1966 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, December 1966 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, January 1967 – February 1967 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, March 1967 – May 1967 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, June 1967 – August 1967 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, September 1967 – December 1967 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, January 1968 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, February 1968 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, March 1968 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, April 1968 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, May 1968 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, June 1968 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, July 1968 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, August 1968 – September 1968 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Correspondence, January 1969 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Meeting Minutes and Agendas: State Board of Education and State Board of Vocational Education, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Meeting Minutes and Agendas: State Board of Education and State Board of Vocational Education, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Meeting Minutes and Agendas: State Board of Education and State Board of Vocational Education, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Meeting Minutes and Agendas: State Board of Education and State Board of Vocational Education, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Publications: “Designing Education For The Future,”, January 1968 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Board of Education—Teacher’s Union, December 1961 – October 1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Series 5: Catholic Church, 1966 – 1975
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Program, No Date (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Installation of Manuel D. Moreno, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Bisbee Parish Council, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, By-Laws, No Date (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, January 1965 - March 1965 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, April 1965 - August 1965 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, October 1965 – December 1965 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, January 1966 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, February 1966 – August 1966 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, September 1966 – November 1966 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Catholic Charities, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Publications: "Selection Of Bishops Process: A Report To The Senate of Priests of the Diocese of Tucson,", 1976 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Publications: "Palo Verde Foundation For Mental Health: Proposed Retirement Plans With Cost Data For Plan Year Ending, June 30, 1976" (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Tucson Diocesan Priorities Committee, 1976 – 1977 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Tucson Diocesan Priorities Committee, Survey and Survey Results, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Volunteer Activity—Catholic Church—Tucson Diocesan Priorities Committee, Survey and Survey Results, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Series 6: Cochise County Hospital Association / Copper Queen Hospital Association
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, 1960s (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, April 1973 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, February 1975-August 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, September 1975-October 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, November 1975-December 1975 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, January 1976-February 1976 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, March 1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, April 1976 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, May 1976 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, June 1976 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association— Correspondence, July 1976 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, August 1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, July 1976-August 1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, September 1976 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, October 1976 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, November 1976-December 1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, January 1977 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, February 1977 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, March 1977 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, April 1977 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, May 1977 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, June 1977 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, July 1977-August 1977 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, September 1977-December 1977 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Cochise County Hospital Association—Correspondence, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Series 7: Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona, 1976 – 1978
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, January 1975-August 1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, June 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, July 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, August 1976-September 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, September 1976-December 1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, January 1977-July 1977 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, August 1977-September 1977 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, October 1977-November 1977 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, December 1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, December 1977 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, January 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, February 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, March 1978 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, April 1978-May 1978 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, June 1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, October 1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, December 1978 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, February 1979-March 1979 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, May 1979 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, June 1979-August 1979 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, October 1979-November 1979 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, January 1980-November 1980 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Health Systems Agency of Southeastern Arizona—Correspondence, March 1981-April 1981 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Series 8: Arizona State Hospital, 1958 - 1965
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, April 1958 - December 1958 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, January 1959 - May 1960 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, June 1960 - December 1960 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, January 1961 - December 1961 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, January 1962 - April 1962 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, May 1962 - December 1962 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, January 1963 - June 1963 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, January 1964 - February 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Correspondence, January 1965 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Meeting Minutes/Reports, May 1958 - December 1958 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Meeting Minutes/Reports, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Meeting Minutes/Reports, January 1960 - June 1960 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Meeting Minutes/Reports, July 1960 - December 1960 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Meeting Minutes/Reports, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Meeting Minutes/Reports, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona State Hospital—Meeting Minutes/Reports, January 1963 - April 1963 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Series 9: League of Arizona Cities and Towns, 1958 - 1960
    - Volunteer Activity—League of Arizona Cities and Towns—Correspondence, May 1958 - December 1958 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—League of Arizona Cities and Towns—Correspondence, January 1959 - December 1959 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—League of Arizona Cities and Towns—Correspondence, January 1960 - August 1960 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—League of Arizona Cities and Towns—Meeting Minutes, October 1958 - April 1960 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—League of Arizona Cities and Towns—Publications: "Arizona Information Bulletin,", 1959 - 1960 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Series 10: University of Arizona College of Law
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors, 1967 – 1968 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors, 1970, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors, 1971-1972 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors—Catalogs, 1973-1977 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors—Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors—Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors—Correspondence, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors—Correspondence, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors—Correspondence, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity—University of Arizona College of Law—Board of Visitors—pamphlet, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Series 11: Miscellaneous Activity
    - Volunteer Activity—American Field Service, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Electric Power Cooperative, Inc., No Date (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Volunteer Activity—Arizona Tomorrow Incorporated, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Volunteer Activity—Bisbee organ concerts, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Volunteer Activity—Bisbee Country Club, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Volunteer Activity—Henry and Barbara Kiker memorial fund and lecture, December 1964-January 1966 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer Activity—Kiwanis Club, 1959-1968 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Volunteer Activity—Miscellaneous, No Date (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Volunteer Activity—Partners of the Alliance, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Volunteer Activity—San Jose community association, 1959-1961 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer Activity—Tucson Boys Chorus, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activity--University of Arizona Alumni Association, 1951-1953 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activity--University of Arizona Alumni Association, 1955-1960, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Activity—YMCA summer camp, 1977-1979 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Subgroup 3: Legal / Business, 1929 - 2002
  "Legal/Business," consists of materials collected from his legal and business practices. Series One contains an alphabetical listing of his legal files. Because of the confidential nature of these files, Series one is closed to researchers until the year 2028. Series Two contains items from his business files relating to Cochise Junior College and DSET. Series Three contains correspondence and memo files from 1993 through 2002, while he was practicing law with the firm of Brown and Bain in Tucson.
  - Series 1: Legal Case Files
    - Legal Files—Arizona criminal court revision committee, March 1973-September 1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—Arizona groundwater management study commission, March 1979-May 1979 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Arizona groundwater management study commission, June 1979-August 1979 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Arizona justices of the peace—annual judicial conference, March 1981-May 1981 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Bisbee—Application for assistance, March 17, 1976-April 19, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—Bisbee—Committee on the sale of Pythian castle and Bisbee jail, January 1973 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—Bisbee—twin cities, June 1974-October 1974 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Bisbee—twin cities, December 1974-May 1975 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—CASA, January 1973-September 1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Cochise Alcoholism Council, February 1973-September 1973 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files—Cochise Alcoholism Council, May 1975-November 1977 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files—Concerned citizens for total representation—correspondence, December 1977 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—Concerned citizens for total representation—correspondence, January 1978-March 1978 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Concerned citizens for total representation—correspondence, April 1978-May 1978 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Concerned citizens for total representation—correspondence, June 1978-December 1978 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Concerned citizens for total representation—, January 1979-April 1979 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—Council of Aging, April 1975-August 1975 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, July 1971, July 1973-December 1973 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, No Date (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, January 1974 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, July 1974-August 1974 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, September 1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, October 1974-November 1974 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, December 1974 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, No Date (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, January 1975-February 1975 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—Court reorganization, April 1975-October 1975, February 1976 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Emergency services file, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Giswald’s motor hotel, September 1974-June 1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Healthcare liability study council, November 1976-September 1977 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—E.F. Hutton and Company, March 1966-July 1972 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—E.F. Hutton and Company—receipts, 1966-1970 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Judge pro tempore, No Date (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Kendall, John, October 1979-December 1979 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Kennedy, Elsie—contracts, April 1972-August 1975 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files—Kerley, Tom and Barney, February 1979-March 1979 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files—Kessier, Averyell A., November 1978-February 1979 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—Kiwanis Club of Bisbee—Articles of Incorporation, November 1963-July 1982 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Kleinman, Richard, December 1978-January 1979 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Knight, Frank, June 1972-April 1979 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Kucharski, Dan, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—Kuykendall, Kate, November 1980-August 1982 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—Lamay, Herbert, September 1981-November 1981 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Lamb, Wilbur, September 1980 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Lane and Estes Farm, inc., December 1963-September 1964 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Lane and Estes Farm, inc., October 1964-August 1967 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files—Lane and Estes Farm, inc., December 1968-July 1969 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files—Lee, Andrew B., August 1980 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Legal Files—Lehner, Ed—tax returns, 1967-1981 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Legal Files—Lehner, Ed—Lehner Farms—Articles of Incorporation, March 1983-November 1954 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—Lehner, Ed—Lehner Farms—minutes, March 1953-December 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Lehner, Ed and Ethlyn—wills, April 1972-March 1973 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Lehner, Ed and Ethlyn—wills, December 1975-September 1980 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Lehner, Ed and Ethlyn—general, March 1953-December 1981 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—Lindsey, Mabel and Howard—trust, January 1980-December 1980 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—Little, W.W., September 1963-April 1968 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Little, W.W., May 1968-July 1968 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Little, W.W., September 1968-December 1982 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Lockhart, Brian, June 1981-August 1982 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files—Loiseau—purchase of Sin of Cortez Bar and Ricardo’s, September 1969-May 1977 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files—Loiseau—purchase of Sin of Cortez Bar and Ricardo’s, June 1977-June 1979 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files—Loya, Jose E., June 1971-September 1974 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Loya, Jose, E., October 1974-January 1977 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files—Luch, Michael and Mary, May 1967-April 1981 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Legal Files—Lyndeborough, New Hampshire, March 1976-June 1976 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Legal Files—Macdonald, Betty, June 1981 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Legal Files—Macia, James H., March 1947-May 1947 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Legal Files—Macia, James H., June 1947 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Legal Files—Macia, James H., July 1947-December 1947 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Legal Files—Macia, James H., February 1948-October 1948 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Legal Files—Macia, James H., March 1949-October 1949 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Legal Files—Macia, James H., March 1950-May 1951 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Legal Files— Macia, James H., April 1952-December 1952 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Legal Files— Macia, James H., January 1953-June 1953 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Legal Files— Macia, James H., January 1954-May 1954 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Legal Files—Mackey, Franklin O.—Gadsdon Hotel, August 1927-March 1950 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Legal Files— Mackey, Franklin O.—B.A. Randall transaction, August 1925 (Box 67, Folder 6)